Brittanie Clare Barrett

britt.barrett13@gmail.com | (310) 940-2409 | Denver, CO 80205

www.linkedin.com/in/brittaniecbarrett/ | github.com/brittbarrett | brittbarrett.github.io/Personal-Profile /index.html

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Senior Client Success Manager and outstanding performer in client communications and digital campaign management. Recognized for inspiring team members to excel and encouraging creative work environments. Enthusiastic and eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Motivated to apply and grow development coding skills and three years of tech marketing experience to a new position with long-term potential.

WORK HISTORY

Wayin Inc.. Denver, CO

Senior Customer Success Manager | 05/2018 - Current
Wayin was acquired by Cheetah Digital in July of 2019
As a Senior Customer Success Manager at Wayin, I strive to help our
sports clientele achieve success with their digital engagement strategy.
With the landscape of digital advertising and engagement constantly on
the change, I help enterprise clients stay on top of trends.

- Primary customer contact available for best practice, ideation, strategy and activation advice.
- Provide client support for platform training needs.
- Go-to for campaign assistance as well as best practice and strategic digital and social marketing advice.

Wayin Inc.. Denver, CO
Sales Representative | 10/2017 - 05/2018

- Lead gen for both senior sales and marketing teams
- Coordinate meetings for senior sales team, create email marketing content, handle both inbound and outbound sales, client content moderation
- Demonstrate the company's platform to potential customers

SKILLS

- Client success
- Market research
- Project Management
- Communications management
- Strategic planning
- Digital marketing
- Campaign management
- [Tech] marketing background
- Social media
- Inside & Outside sales
- Brand awareness
- Team leadership
- Digital media integration
- Strategic marketing

EDUCATION

Santa Clara University Santa Clara, CA 06/2017

BBA: Marketing Technology

- Member of [Alpha Phi Sorority]
- Majored in [Technology Marketing]

John Felice Rome Center Rome, Italy

• 6 month study abroad program

University of DenverDenver, CO

Flex LTD. Santa Clara, CA Project Manager Intern | 06/2016 - 09/2016

- Global entity that designs, manufactures, and distributes a variety of technology products worldwide
- Became sufficient in Tableau software, manipulating and analyzing data in order to create data visualizations suitable for the CIO and individual departments to make valuable business spending decisions regarding license/vendor management.
- Received top marks for my presentation of my internship experience, which included the data visualizations I created and how the various executives utilized those visualizations.

SCU Bronco Bench Foundation, Santa Clara University, . Santa Clara, CA

Sports Marketing Intern | 01/2014 - 06/2015

Working directly for the head of the Bronco Bench Foundation, I was
responsible for updating the finances for the athletic department,
making calls for donations, handling logistics for alumni athletic
gatherings, and marketing for various athletic events on campus.

CloudVelox. San Jose, CA

Market Research Intern | 06/2015 - 09/2015

- Provider of cloud automation software
- Created and presented a survey to IT Executives of prospective clients Cold-called to IT Executives and compiled the survey data into a report for CloudVelox's management team.
- The survey focused on the different Disaster Recovery (DR) plans used by those companies and whether or not they would be willing to migrate to a cloud-based DR plan.

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

 Currently enrolled in DU's full-stack development coding bootcamp and will graduate from the program September, 2020.